Desmond  我要你回到牛津大学
Desmond. I need you to go back to Oxford University.
去我们相遇的地方
Go back to where we met.
我要你去那找我妈  她名叫
I need you to go there and find my mother. Her name is--
如果我没法把他们都弄回来  会怎样
What happens if I can't get them all to come back?
那就只有上帝保佑了
Then god help us all.
我今天要返回小岛上
I'm going back to the island today...
只要我做一件事
Just as soon as I do one thing--
杀了你的女儿
Kill your daughter.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
Desmond
他身体在变冷
He's coding!
-枪伤  他不行了  -7号手术室  快点
- Gunshot wound. He's crashing. - Bay 7. now!
-他还好吧  -请你在这等着  女士
- Is he gonna be okay? - You're gonna have to wait here, ma'am.
你带他去哪  要带他去哪里
Where are you--where are you taking him?
稍安勿躁  我们一知道情况会
Please ma'ma. Wait here,we'll let you know as soon as
-马上通知你的  -怎么了他会好吗
- We know anything. - What's happening? Is he gonna be ok?
我们会尽力的
We'll going to do everything we can.
请耐心等待
Please just wait
-爸爸  -他会好的  他会好的
- Daddy - He's gonna be okay. he's gonna be okay.
孩子多大了
How old is your son?
两岁
He's 2.
和他父亲一样的头发
He has his father's hair.
抱歉  我认识你吗
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
你不认识  但你丈夫认识我
Uh, no, but your husband does.
我是Eloise Hawking
I'm Eloise Hawking
我相信Desmond中枪
And I believe it's my son's fault
都是因为我儿子犯下的错
That Desmond has been shot.
你儿子是Benjamin Linus吗
Your son is Benjamin Linus?
怎么可能
Good lord, no.
我儿子是Daniel Farady
My son is Dniel Faraday.
三十年前
Thirty Years Earlier
嘿  能搭把手吗
Hey, can I get a hand with this?
好的  好的
Yeah, yeah.
Dan
Dan.
Miles  好久不见
Hey, Miles. Long time no see.
注意了  先生女士们
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
你们知道为何而来  我祝你们睡好
You know why you're here. I wish you could all get
-来这里的第一觉  但是...  -你
- A good night's sleep, but, uh... - What
回来干嘛  Dan
the hell are you doing back,Dan?
我以为你去安阿伯发大财了
Once you left for ann arbor, I figured you'd gotten rich,
发明DVD什么的
Invented the dvd or something.
这就是我为什么要回来
This is what I'm doing back here.
-他们什么时候来的
- When did they get here?
不久前
A few days ago.
真奇怪  对吧
It's weird, huh?
没时间了  我要你
We don't have time. I need you
马上带我去Jack哪里  好吗
To take me to Jack's right now, okay?
-Jack  你怎么回的  -Farady  你
- Jack. how did you get back here? - Faraday? what the--
你怎么做到的
How did you do it?
-你怎么回到岛上的  -你去哪里了
- How did you get back to the island? - where have you been?
我去达摩总部做研究  在安阿伯
I was--I was just at Dharma headquarters  in ann arbor. I was doing some research.
现在更加重要的是
What's more important right now...
-你怎么回到1977年的  -怎么回事
- How did you get back here to 1977? - what's going on?
-别看我  我只帮他提箱子  -Jack  怎样来的
- Don't look at me. I just carried his luggage. - Jack, how?
嗯...我们坐飞机  然后...
Uh... we were on a plane, and then there was--
谁告诉你坐飞机的
Who told you to get on a plane?
事实上  Dan  是你的母亲
As a matter of fact, Dan, it was your mother.
那么她是怎样说服你的  Jack
And how did she convince you, Jack?
她告诉你这是你的宿命吗
Did she tell you it was your destiny?
对  她就这么说的
Yeah. That's exactly what she said.
我得告诉你点坏消息  Jack
Well, I got some bad news for you, Jack.
你根本就不属于这里
You don't belong here at all.
她错了
She was wrong.
怎么了  妈妈  你不喜欢吗
What's wrong, mom? Didn't you like it?
我喜欢得不行
I loved it.
太美妙了  Daniel
It was beautiful, Daniel.
Daniel
Daniel...
你知道命运是什么吗
Do you know what destiny means?
不知道
No.
命运就是
Destiny means that,
如果你有天赋
If one has a special gift,
那么你一定得去发挥它
Then it must be nurtured.
从你开始弹奏
How many beats has that metronome counted
一共有多少拍
Since you started playing?
864拍
864.
Daniel  你的天赋是  头脑
Your gift, daniel, is your mind--
一颗为科学和数学而生的头脑
A mind that is meant for science, mathematics.
而我的任务是
And it's my... job
确保你那样发展下去
To keep you on your path.
那么  不幸地是
So... unfortunately,
我不能给你太多的时间  让你分心
There's no more time... for distractions.
但是我想一直弹钢琴
But I want to keep playing the piano.
我可以两样兼顾
I can do both.
我能挤时间
I can make time.
那就等你能挤出时间再说
If only you could.
Miles  我要你带我去兰花站
Miles, I need you to bring me to the orchid.
你能现在载我去吗  求你了
Can you drive me right now? please?
-好  好的  -谢了
- Yeah, yeah, sure. I guess. - thanks.
来吧  我们出发
Come on. let's go.
Faraday  等等
Faraday! Wait up!
Miles  快点  Jack  我们马上回来
Miles, come on. Jack, we'll be right back.
你说你妈妈错了是什么意思  Daniel
Hey, what did you mean, you mother was wrong? daniel!
我去办点事  马上回来
I just--I just have an errand to run. Be right back!
-怎么  -Faraday回来了
- Yeah? - Faraday's back.
这话什么意思  为什么回来
What do you mean Faraday's back? Why?
我也不知道  他坐潜艇来  把我叫醒
I have no idea. He came in on the sub, and he woke me up.
就神神叨叨
He--he started talking nonsense,
然后就出发去兰花站了
And then he took off for the orchid.
很喜欢听你这套  但我现在有点忙
I'd love to trade theories about this,I'm little busy right now.
清晨6点  你忙什么
What are you busy in the 6 morning?
James  告诉他吧
James, tell him.
进来吧
Get in here.
Phil 我的一个保安手下
Phil-- one of my security guys--
发现一盒有我和Kate的录像带
Got himself a videotape of me and kate
带着那小孩去找那帮敌人
Taking the kid out to the hostiles.
-录像带呢  -Phil那里
- And where's the tape? - With phil.
Phil呢?
And where is phil?
Phil 这是Jack  Jack 这是Phil
Phil, jack. jack... phil.
我们是..
Are we...
在等什么吗
Waiting for something?
时间刚刚好
Right on time.
我10分钟后回来
I'll be back in ten minutes.
那你要我做什么
So what do you want me to do?
你什么都不用做
You're gonna do nothing.
如果你再钻深一厘米
If you drill even 1 centimeter further,
你将有可能释放那个能量
You risk releasing that energy.
如果这事发生了的话
If that were to happen...
那么就让上帝保佑我们吧
Then god help us all.
你在这里要带安全帽
Hey! you need a hard hat down here.
走路带眼
Watch yourself!
对不起 不会再这样了
Sorry, sir. Won't happen again.
我来拿一些东西  我们走
I'll grab the rest of his stuff. Let's go.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
时空旅行  那人以为我们有多蠢
Time travel. How stupid does that guy think we are?
陈博士
Dr. Chang?
-有空吗  -看来有
- Do you have a second, sir? - I suppose.
我刚和潜艇上的天鹅队
I just came in on the sub with the swan team.
其实我们三年前见过  我是Daniel Faraday
We actually met three years ago, I'm Daniel Faraday.
你和Lafleur一起来的  我记得
Yes. yes. uh, you arrived with Lafleur. I remember. right.
我能帮你什么忙
What can I do for you?
我需要你下命令
I need you to order the evacuation
让岛上所有男女老少撤离这座岛
Of every man, woman and child on this island.
我凭什么这么做呢
And why would I do that?
因为担架上的那个人
Because that man is on a stretcher
就是你们在这里钻着泄露出来
As a consequence of the electromagnetic activity
电磁效应的后果
That your drilling unleashed down here.
而且这里充满了
Which is now contained.
这里充满了
It's contained down here.
但大约6小时后
But in about six hours,
同样的事情会在
The same thing is gonna happen
天鹅站的地方发生
At the site for the swan station,
不同的是那个能量 大约是刚才的3万倍
Only the energy there is about 30,000 times more powerful sir.
而那事故
And the accident...
会是场大灾难
It's gonna be catastrophic.
这绝对是无稽之谈
That is utterly absurd.
你凭什么做出这样的预测呢
What could possibly qualify you to make that kind of prediction?
我来自未来
I'm from the future.
等等  陈博士
Dr. Chang, wait!
能等一会吗  就一会
Will you wait one second, please? Wait one--one second.
好的  你来自未来
Yes, yes, you come from the future.
你听到我谈论时空旅行
You heard me talking out time travel.
现在你开足玩笑了  恭喜你
Now you've had your fun. Good for you
求求你别
no, no. ple
请你看看这本日记  看看这些公式
Just look at my journal, please. Look at these equations.
某些人再过20年都不会被发现
Some of them won't be discovered for another 20 years.
陈博士
Dr. Chang
Dan  别骚扰他
Hey! hey! hey, Dan! Leave the man alone.
对不起陈博士  我想他在潜艇嗑太多药
Sorry, Dr. Chang. I think he had too many drugs on the sub--
陈博士
Dr. Chang...
Miles是你的儿子
Miles is your son.
-你说什么  -想想吧
- Excuse me? - Think about it.
一个叫Miles的中国人  和你的孩子同名
A chinese man named miles-- the same name as your baby--
和我一起来自未来
Shows up with me from the future.
你真以为这些都是巧合吗
You--you really think this is all coincidence?
这是真的吗
Is this true?
不
No.
拜托
Please...
离我远点
Stay away from me.
陈博士
Dr. Chang...
你是疯了吗
If you-- hey! hey! hey! Are you out of your mind?
-你干嘛呢  -我只想让你父亲
- What are you doing? - I'm making sure
去做他该做的事
That your father does what he's supposed to do.
要他做什么
And what's that?
你会知道的
You'll see.
妈
Hi, mom.
我想你见见Theresa
I want you to meet Theresa.
-Dan跟我说了很多  -很高兴见到你
- Dan's told me so much about - Pleased to meet you.
干得好  Daniel
Well done, Daniel.
你肯定很为他自豪
Ah... you much be so proud of him.
Daniel我认为我们可以用午餐来庆祝你的成就
Daniel, I thought we could celebrate your accomplishment With lunch.
附近有家不错的餐厅  我定了位子
There's a nice restaurant nearby. I reserved us a table.
我们很乐意
We would love to.
事实上我很希望只有我们两个
Actually, I was hoping it would be just the two of us.
你会理解的吧
You do understand, don't you?
只是不习惯见到我孩子和别人一起
It's just that I haven't high tempt to see my son very oft.
我理解  母亲
Mother... I understand.
没事的  Dan  真的
It's okay, Dan. Really.
Daniel  有什么烦恼的吗
Is there something bothering you, Daniel?
你对Theresa很无礼
You were so rude to Theresa.
-我有吗  -Theresa是我女朋友
- Was I? - Theresa is my girlfriend.
她是你的试验助理
She is your research assistant.
你应该集中尽力进行工作
You should be focusing your energies on your work.
-我的工作  -是的  那很重要
- On my work. - Yes. That is what is important.
你说得很清楚了
Yes. You've made it abundantly clear.
为什么我会把天赋浪费在一个女人身上
Why would I waste my gift on a woman--
很抱歉告诉你  Daniel
I'm sorry to tel! Daniel
但你没有时间去谈恋爱
But you're not going to have time for relationships.
这个女人在你生命中会是场痛
The women in your life will only be terribly hurt.
你什么意思呢
What does that mean?
我是说你应该一直工作第一  就这些
It means that your work will always comes first, that's all.
就因为你一直逼我这么做
Only because that's what you always push me to do.
你一再逼我
You pushed and you pushed and you pushed.
何时才是尽头啊  母亲  何时
And when will it be enough, mother? When?
我是牛津历史上 毕业的博士中最年轻的
I'm the youngest doctorate ever To ever graduatl from Oxford
我刚拿到了150万英镑的研究资助
I just got a new 1.5 million pound research grant.
-我还需要做什么呢  -资助
- What else do I have to do? - A grant?
太棒了  谁给的
That's wonderful! From whom?
我不知道
I don't know. um...
某个资本家吧
Some industrialist.
Widmore  我猜是
Widmore, I think.
Charles Widmore
Charles Widmore.
我不想和你吵  Daniel
I don't want to fight with you, Daniel.
我不是为这个而来的
That's not why I came.
那你为何而来
Why did you come?
来恭喜你
To congratulate you.
好运  Daniel
Good luck, Daniel.
我希望你认为我是真心实意地
And I do hope you know that I mean that.
大家听好
All right, people.
快乐时光结束了
Party's over.
我知道你们刚来岛上
I know y'all just showed up.
而我们则已经在岛上呆了3年整了
The rest of us have been here for the past three years.
我最不想做的就是离开这里
The last thing I wanna do is leave.
-但我们没得选择  -关在壁橱
- But we ain't got no choice. - Well, that dude
里面的那个人  我还以为他是你手下
In the closet-- I thought he worked for you.
难道你就不能说服他这就是个
Can't you convince him that it was all, like,
-误会吗  -我就在这
- A misunderstanding? - I punched
地方打晕的这个人啊  Hugo
The man in the damn place Hugo
你要我怎么解释呢  我失手吗
What am I supposed to say-- "my fi slipped"?
在别人发觉到他失踪之前  我们
How much time do we have before someone
-还有多少时间呢  -不够逃走的
-Realizes he's go. - Not enough
那我们该怎么办
So where do we go?
我们只有两种办法
We only got two options.
要么我们去夺取潜艇
We can either commandeer the sub,
在别人发觉我们消失之前逃离这破岛
Get the hell off this island before anyone knows we're gone,
或者我们可以回到丛林里去
Or we can head back in the jungle,
从头开始
Start from square one.
只要有一丝机会我老婆还在岛上的话
I'm not getting on that sub
我就不会上那潜艇的
If there's a chance that my wife is still on this island now
我也是  我们大费周章的回到这里
Yeah, me either. After all we did to get back here?
而现在我们又一走了之吗
And now we're just gonna run off again?
这就有些滑稽
It'd be kinda wishy-washy.
现在有两票赞同从头开始的  其他人
Right. That's two votes for square one. Anybody else wanna..
稍等  马上来
Hold your horses. Be right there.
你好  James
Hey, James.
欢迎加入圆桌会议  变态
Welcome to the meeting, twitchy.
再次见到你真好
Good to see you again.
蛋糕在厨房  会议上不要约束
Pound cake's in the kitchen. Help yourself to the punch.
-他还是那么疯吗  -现在是全新境界
- Is he still crazy? - It's on a whole new level, man.
好
Great.
Jack  很抱歉先前没礼貌
Jack, I'm sorry I was rude before,
但我 到这里来对屋里每个人来说都很重要
but what I came to do Is of critical importance to everyone in this room.
有人知道怎样才能找到那些敌人呢
Does anyone know where I can find the hostiles?
你为什么想知道呢  Daniel
Why do you need to know that, Daniel?
因为我母亲是其中之一
Because one of them is my mother.
而她是这个岛上唯一
And she is the only person on this island
可以让我们回到属于我们世界的人
Who can get us back to where we belong.
打捞行动来自
This hunting fully comes to us from
Christian一号  印度洋上的解救船
The "Christiane I," a salvage vehicle in the indian ocean.
-Dan你想吃怎样的煎蛋  -它在
- How do you want your eggs, Dan? - For more than two months,
他们一直在探索这个深度的
It's been scouring the depths
怎么了  他们发现了那架失踪的飞机吗
So what happened? They found that missing plane?
寻找失踪已久的大洋航班815号
In search of the long-missing oceanic flight 815.
-Dan  -昨晚Christiane号部署
- Dan? - Late last night, the" christiane"deployed
两架远程遥控的机器  ROVs
Two remotely operated vehicles, or R.O.Vs...
Dan  你怎么这么伤心
Dan. Why are so upset?
这个证实了
That verified what
国家运输安全局一直以来担心
The National Transportation Safety Board had long feared...
-我也不知道为什么  -那架商务航空
- I don'know. - That the commercial aircraft...
在2004年11月22号
On september 22nd, 2004...
有人来看你了  Dan
You have a visitor, Dan.
您想喝点茶吗
Would you like some tea?
非常感谢
That would be lovely.
你好  Daniel
Hello, Daniel.
对不起先生  我不...
I'm sorry, sir. I don't...
Caroline跟您说我我有病吗
D-did Caroline tell you I have a condition
这个会影响我的记忆  就会
That affects my memory? Just...
别担心  我们没有见过
Don't be embarrassed. We've never met.
我是Charles Widmore
My name is Charles Widmore.
Charles
Charles...
Charles widmore
Charles widmore from...
资助我的研究的那个
My research grant?
很高兴见到您  请坐
It's very nice to meet you, sir. Please, sit down.
这儿很乱
Mm, a bit of a mess.
我很想感谢您
I meant to thank you
在我
Before I...
在我离开牛津之前
Before I left oxford.
你是说再你被开除之前
You mean, before you were dismissed.
我实验过
I tested it...
我事先在我身上做的实验
I tested it out on myself first.
-没事的  Daniel  -我绝不会伤害theresa
- It's all right, Daniel. - I would never hurt Theresa.
没事的
It's all right.
我不是为这个而来
That's not why I'm here.
我来是给你一个新的机会的
I came to offer you a new opportunity.
不  我...
N-no, I...
对不起  我不能  我想我不能...
I'm sorry. I...I can't. I don't think I...I can...
我说了什么令你伤心的话吗
Did I say something to upset you?
是那场飞机失事
It's this plane crash.
我不知道为什么这让我如此烦恼
I don't know why it's bothering me so much.
就是这么悲伤
It's just so sad.
他们都死了
They're dead.
Daniel  如果我告诉你
Daniel, what if I told you...
他们并没有死
They're not dead?
如果我告诉你
What if I told you
那飞机是个替代品
The plane was a fake?
人为设置的  昂贵的替代品
An elaborate... expensive fake.
你怎么知道的呢
How would you know that?
因为是我设置的
Because I put it there.
为什么要告诉我呢
Why would you tell me that?
因为到了明天  你就不记得我说过
Because come tomorrow, you won't remember I did.
Daniel
Daniel,
真正的大洋航班815号坠毁到一个岛上
The real oceanic flight 815 crashed on an island-
一个特别的小岛上
A special island
岛上有独特的科学性质
With unique scientific properties.
我想派你去那座岛
I want to send you to the island.
那会对你的研究很有帮助
It will further your research,
给你展现各种
Show you things
你未曾想象过的现象
You'd never dream of.
但更重要的是
But more importantly,
它会治愈你的  Daniel
It will heal you, Daniel
你的心智
Your mind,
你的记忆
Your memory.
治愈我吗
H-heal me?
你为什么为我这么做呢
W-why are you doing all this for me?
因为你是个很有才华的人
Because you're a man of tremends gifts,
把这些才华浪费掉是很可耻的
And it would be a shame to see them go to waste.
你说话像我母亲
You sound like my mother.
因为我们是老朋友
That's because we're old friends.
你母亲是另一个
You're mother is an other?
实际上你见过她
You met her, actually,
当这岛消失回到1954年时
When the island was skipping, back in 1954.
他们叫她Ellie
They were calling her "Ellie."
你们去过1954年
You guys were in 1954?
-像冻结时间吗  -你还没有
- Like... fonzie times? - You still haven't
告诉我们为什么要找到她
Told us why you need find her.
我只要跟她谈谈
I just need to talk to her.
医生说我们理应死了的
Doc said we are supposed to be laid low
木已成舟
"whatever happened, happened"?
只是告诉我他们在哪
Just tell me where they  are
我不会告诉你任何事  你也别想
I'm not telling you anything, and you ain't
去任何地方  除非
Going anywhere, unless you wanna
你告诉我们你在这到底干什么
Share with us what the hell it is you're doing.
Sawyer  他说他能带我们回到属于我们的世界
Sawyer, he said he can get us back to where we belonged.
不管是上潜艇还是回到丛林
Whether we go on the sub or we head back into the jungle...
-我们不只属于这里  -可我属于
- We don't belong here. - Well, I belonged
这里  却发现你回来了  医生
Here just fine out you came back, doc.
你知道敌人在哪吗
You know where the hostiles are.
-说什么  -你和Sawyer带Ben去找他们
- What? - You and Sawyer took Ben out to them.
你能带我们去吗
Can you get us back out there?
打住  别说任何话  Kate
Hold on a second. Don't say a word, Kate..
她想说什么就说什么  Kate
She can say what she wants to say. Kate...
你要我发誓从不过问Aron怎么了
You made me promise to never ask what happened to Aron,
又或者为什么你回到这里
Or why you came back here.
但我知道原因没有藏在这里
But I know that reason isn't... it isn't here.
也不是现在
It's not now.
不管她是什么原因
Whatever her reason is,
带这个疯子去和她妈谈
Helping H.G. wells here talk to his mommy
绝对和这没有关系
Ain't got nothing to do with it.
跟我们走  雀斑女
Come with us, Freckles.
防护栏的密码 是141717
The code for the fence Is 1-4-1-7-1-7.
你该带Daniel去
You should take Daniel.
怎么都好 这里对我们来说已经结束了
It's over here for us anyway.
好吧
Okay.
我们走
Let's go.
太好了
Great.
太好了  谢谢
Great. Thank you.
Miles  你能开车带我们吗
Hey, Miles, can you drive us?
当你意识到你犯了多么大的错误时
When you realize you've made a huge mistake...
我们会回到海岸边  在我们开始的地方
We'll be back at the beach, right where we started.
好了  剩下的这些人
All right, the rest of us--
带好你需要的物品  20分钟后这里见
Pack anything you can carry, meet back here in 20 minutes.
该出发了
Time to go.
这些人不会高兴见到我们的
These people are not gonna be happy to see us.
也许带些几把枪是个好主意
It might be a good idea to bring some guns.
发动机的棚子里有个枪支保险箱 但是锁了
There's a gun safe in the motor pool, But it's locked.
还好我是看门的
Good thing I'm a janitor then.
Dan
Hey, Dan?
我去发动机棚子找你们  给我一分钟 行吧
I'll meet you at the motor pool. I need just a minute. Okay?
他们不准我在饭前吃巧克力的
I'm not allowed to have chocolate before dinner.
亲爱的  没事的
It's okay, sweetheart.
我不会揭发你
I won't tell.
我叫Charlotte  你叫什么
My name's Charlotte. What's yours?
我叫Daniel
I'm Daniel.
我是新来的
I'm new here.
听好
Listen.
你认识陈博士吗
Do you know Dr. Chang?
很快
Hopefully really soon,
陈博士就要让一群人
Dr. Chang is gonna ask a bunch of people
登上潜艇
To get on the submarine
然后离开这座岛
And leave the island.
当他这么做的时候  你和你母亲
When he does, you and your mommy...
你们得离开
You're gonna have to leave.
以防我的方法行不通
In case what I do doesn't work,
你不能呆在这里  你一定得走
You cannot be here. You have to leave.
我不想告诉你这个的
I tried to avoid telling you this.
我不认为我能改变过去
I didn't think I could change things.
但也许我能
But maybe I can.
我们得多久到那里
Hey, how long will it take us to Get up there?
看情况  我们可以走大路到塔那儿
Ah, it depends. We can take the road until we hit the pylons,
一旦我们进入他们攻击范围  就得步行
But then once we're in their territory, we gotta go on foot.
有没有给新手用的
Okay. uh, do you have something for a beginner?
我们走
Let's go.
准备好走
That's ready to go.
出了什么事吗
What's going on here?
你不是潜艇下来的一个物理学家吗
Aren't you one of the physicists off the sub?
对  我们只是想确认下
Yeah, that's right. Uh, we were just making sure that
你应该在天鹅站的
You're supposed to out of the swan site.
兰花站
Right. uh, there was--
出了点事故
There was an accident at the orchid station.
-陈博士我们来帮忙  -他手里有枪
- Dr. Chang asked us to help. - He's got a gun.
我刚从陈博士那里来
I just left Dr. Chang.
他在家陪老婆孩子  你在撒谎
He's at home with his wife and baby. You're lying.
丢掉武器  趴在地上
Now drop the guns and get down on the ground!
听我说
Hey. Listen to me. Listen.
你真的不明白这里发什么什么事
You really do not understand what's happening here.
你不明白  我们没时间了  必须走
You have no idea. We have no time. We have to leave.
行吗  我们现在就走
All right? So we're just gonna leave.
没人
Nobody's...No...
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我们该到车上去
I think we can make it to the jeep.
好的  我掩护你
All right. i'll cover you.
Dan  你也去  好吗
Dan? you go, too, all right?
快  快  快
Go, go, go!
拉响警报
Sound the alarm!
你好  Daniel
Hello, Daniel.
你什么时候来的
When did you get here?
我刚到
Oh, I just arrived.
本想给你先打个电话  可是...
I would have called you, but...
反正我会忘掉的
I would have forgotten anyway.
我听说有人要给你一个工作
I hear you have been offered a job.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我一直都知道
Well, it's my business to know.
Daniel  我来这
I came here, daniel,
是想告诉你  这件事至关重要
To tell you that it is very important
你该答应Widmore先生
That you say yes to Mr. Widmore...
接受这次机会
That you accept this opportunity.
我不能
I can't.
他需要一个
He needs someone who can do
能够校准十分复杂的时空
Really, really complex space-time calibrations
并且计算出方位的人  可是我
And calculate bearings, and I just...
已经不在懂得如何去做了
I don't know how to do that anymore.
Daniel
Daniel...
那个他向你提起的地方  那个小岛
This place he mentioned to you, this island--
他有没有告诉你它可以治好你
Did he tell you that it could make you better?
如果那是真的呢
What if it's true?
怎么了  这样你就可以继续你的工作了
Why, then you could go on with your work.
想想你能完成的事业吧
Just think of all you could accomplish.
你真的想让我...去吗
You really want me to... to go?
是的
Yes.
那...
Will...
这会让你为我感到骄傲吗
Will it make you proud of me?
是的  Daniel
Yes, Daniel.
会的
It will.
好的  我去
Then I'll do it.
-你还记得密码吗  -记得
- You remember the code? - Yeah, I got it.
好的  让我看看
All right, I'm gonna take a look at that.
好的
Yeah, good.
只是擦伤
It's just a graze. Whew.
会有点刺痛
This is gonna sting.
好的
Yeah.
好的  很快就好了
Yeah, you're gonna be fine.
我可真幸运
I guess I'm lucky.
这跟幸运有什么关系
What's luck have to do with it?
你不是说该发生的事  肯定会发生的吗
I thought you said whatever happened, happened.
你会明白的  Jack
You gotta understand, Jack,
这是我们的现在
This is our present.
我们见面时  我的脖子上有疤吗
When we met, did I have a scar on my neck?
没有
No.
那是因为我还没有被枪击
'cause I hadn't been shot yet.
我们不能天真的认为我们不会出事
We can't be so naive as to think nothing can happen to us.
我们中的任何人都会死  Jack
Any one of us can die, Jack.
好的
Okay.
已经关了
It's off.
谢谢
Thanks.
哪条路
Which way?
往里走2英里
Just a couple miles in.
你觉得他知道自己在做什么吗
Do you think he knows what he's doing?
希望如此
I sure hope so.
已经回不了头了
There's no turning back now.
你刚刚给那些蠢货打电话让他们来着
You called it the minute those yahoos got here.
你该告诉我的
I shoulda listened to you.
你可以说  那我也告诉你
You can say, "I told you so."
等我们到了岸上吧
Maybe after we get to the beach.
你还支持我吗
You still got my back?
你呢
You still got mine?
这下糟了
That's not good, right?
Lafleur
Lafleur!
你去哪了
Where have you been? Whoa, whoa, whoa.
别紧张  发生什么事了
Take it easy, stu. What the hell's going on?
我被一个物理学家打了一枪
I just got shot by a physicist,
还有新兵在帮他
And the new recruits are helping him.
我们中有奸细
We've been infiltrated.
太荒唐了  冷静些
That's ridiculous. Now just calm down for a minute.
我们谈谈
We can talk about this.
那是什么
What was that?
好像是从外面传过来的
It sounded like it was from outside.
趴在地上
Get down on the ground now.
马上
I said now!
谢谢
Thank you.
你需要拿着枪跟你妈妈说话吗  Dan
You need a gun to go talk to your mother, Dan?
你不了解我妈妈  Jack
You don't know my mother, Jack.
准备告诉我们为什么她是错的了吗
You ready to tell me why she was wrong?
为什么我们不属于这里
Why we don't belong here?
四个小时之内
In about four hours,
天鹅工作区的达摩组织的人
The dharma folks at the swan work site--
他们将会钻到地下
They're gonna--gonna drill into the ground
并且会意外碰到巨大能量袋
And accidentally tap into a massive pocket of energy.
这个能量的释放
The result of the release of this energy
会造成一场灾难
Would be catastrophic.
为了能够抑制它  他们不得不用水泥
So in order to contain it, they're gonna have to cement
注满整个地区就像切尔诺贝利核电站一样
The entire area in, like chernobyl.
这个容器  就是他们建造它的地方
And this containment--the place they built over it--
我想你叫它船舱
I believe you called it "the hatch."
天鹅船舱
The swan hatch?
因为这场意外
Because of this one accident,
这群人会在接下来20年里
These people is gona spend next twenty years
来抑制那个能量
Keeping that energy at bay...
通过不停的按一个按钮
By pressing a button...
而这个按钮将会被你的朋友Desmond
A button that your friend desmond
在某一天忘了按
Will one day fail to push,
而这个就令到你们做的飞机
And that will cause your plane--
海洋航空815班机
Oceanic 815--
坠毁到这个岛上
To crash on this island.
而因为你们的航班坠毁
And because your plane crashed,
令到有一架货轮被派到这个岛上
A freighter will be sent to this island--
和其他有关的人都在上面
And charlotte was on it and so forth.
这整个相关的一连串事件
This entire chain of events--
将会在今天下午开始发生
It's gonna start happening this afternoon.
可是
But...
我们可以改变这一切
We can change that.
我一生都致力于研究相对物理
I studied relativistic physics my entire life.
有一个观念一直主导着我
One thing emerged over and over--
不可能改变过去  不可能
Can't change the past. Can't do it.
已经发生的  早就发生了
Whatever happened, happened. All right?
可是我最后发现
But then I finally realized...
我花了大量的时间研究
I had been spending so much time
常量
Focused on the constants,
可是我忽略了变量
I forgot about the variables.
Jack  你知道在这些公式里面的变量吗
Do you know what the variables in these equations are, jack?
不知道
No.
我们
Us.
我们是变量
We're the variables.
人
People.
我们思考  我们讲道理
We think. we reason.
我们做不同的选择  我们有自由的思想
We make choices. We have free will.
我们可以改变我们的命运
We can change our destiny.
我认为我可以中和那股能量
I think I can negate that energy
在天鹅站下面的那股
Under e swan.
我想我可以毁灭它
I think I can destroy it.
如果我能的话  那密封舱就不需要被建造
If I can, then that hatch will never be built,
而你们的飞机
And your plane...
将会降落
Your plane will land,
在它应该降落的地方
Just like it's supposed to,
在洛杉矶
In los angeles.
能告诉我你打算怎么去中和这股能量吗
And just how exactly do you plan on destroying this energy?
我将会引爆一个氢弹
I'm gonna detonate a hydrogen bomb.
Daniel Faraday
Daniel faraday?
你儿子是Danial Faraday
Your son is daniel faraday?
是的
Yes.
就是那个叫Desmond去洛杉矶找你的那个
That's the man who sent desmond to los angeles to find you.
是的
That's right.
我来道歉的  Penelope
I came, Penelope, to apologize.
你的丈夫变成一个牺牲品
Your husband has become a casualty
在一场比他  甚至比我们任何一个
In a conflict that's bigger than him,
都重要的冲突里面
That's bigger than any of us.
你在说什么  Desmond会没事吧
What do you mean? Is Desmond gona be OK?
我不知道
I don't know.
在很长的一段时间里面
For the first time in a long time,
我第一次不知道将会发生什么
I don't know what's going to happen next.
-是Humes小姐吗  -是的
- Ms. hume? - Yes
你丈夫在康复室
Your husband's in the recovery room, and he's
-他在找你  -康复室  他
- Asking for you. - The recovery room. Is he...
他情况不错  跟我来吧
He's doing fine. Come with me.
这位护士会照顾你的儿子
This nurse will watch your son.
好吗
Hi.
好
我以为我失去你了
I thought I'd lost you.
我答应过你  Penny
I promised you, Penny.
我答应过的
I promised you...
我永远不会离开你的
I'd never leave you again.
他没事吧
Is he all right?
没事  Charles
Yes, Charles.
他没事
He's fine.
好
Good.
你女儿在里面
Your daughter's in there.
你为何不进出打声招呼
Why don't you go in and say hello?
很不幸的 Eloise
Unfortunately, Eloise,
我和Penelope的关系
My relationship with Penelope
是其中一样我需要牺牲的事情
Is one of the things I had to sacrifice.
牺牲?
Sacrifice?
不要跟我说什么叫做牺牲 Charles
Don't you talk to me about sacrifice, Charles.
我必须把我的儿子送回到那个岛上
I had to send my son back to the island,
而且知道将会....
Knowing full well that--
他也是我的儿子 Eloise
He was my son, too, Eloise.
这是个错误
This is a mistake.
他在提到说
He's talking about
把一切发生过在我们身上的事情抹掉
Erasing everything that's ever happened to us, Jack.
这是疯狂的
It's insane.
我们在一架飞在半空的飞机上消失
We disappeared off a plane in mid-air
来到1977年
And ended up in 1977.
我感觉已经习惯了疯狂
I'm getting kinda used to insane.
这应该够了
Well, that should be enough.
我想我们需要多点水
I think we need more water.
-祝我好运吧  -等等
- Wish me luck. wait. - Hey.
让他走  让他走
No, let him go. Let him go.
退后 让开
Back up. Step away. It's oy.
都不准动
Nobody move.
我只想和Eloise讲话
I only want to speak to Eloise.
Eloise在那里
Where is Eloise?
快点  她在那里
Come on. where is she?
对不起  不过Eloise
I'm sorry, but Elo--
她现在不在这里
She's not here right now.
我们认识吗
Do we know each other?
这个无关重要
It doesn't matter.
我要你带我去见Eloise
I need you to take me to Eloise.
我已经告诉过你她不在这里
I-I already told you she's not here.
-轻松点  -那个炸弹在哪里 Richard
- Let's just take it easy. - Where's the bomb, richard?
我告诉过你的那个氢弹
The hydrogen bomb that I told you
叫你们埋起来的那个
People to bury where is it?
听我的放下枪  我们来谈一谈  好不
Listen to me. Lower your gun, and we'll talk. Okay?
我们不想有人受伤  把枪放下
Nobody has to get hurt here. Just put the gun down.
我给你三秒钟
I'm gonna give you three seconds.
-一  -不要这么做
- One... - Don't do this.
二
Two...
-你干嘛这么做  -他用枪指着你呢
- Why did you do that? - He had a gun on you.
他不会开枪的  Eloise
He wasn't gonna shoot me, Eloise.
Eloise
Eloise.
你知道的
You knew.
你一直都知道的
You always knew.
你知道这将会发生
You knew this was gonna happen.
你把我派到这里来
You sent me here.
你是谁
Who are you?
我
I...
我是你儿子
I'm your son.